

CONTACT

- @ adrianodiazb@gmail.com
- 652 11 18 38
- www.github.com/PublioElio
- in www.es.linkedin.com/in/adrianodiaz

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Spring Boot
- SQL-PL/SQL
- Android development (Java)
- HTML CSS
- Linux (bash scripting)
- JUnit
- Selenium
- **QA** and test automation
- Atlassian Jira
- Python
- C#
- JavaScript

LANGUAGES

Advanced Certificate of English (Cambridge) C1

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco CCNA: Introduction to Networks

Cisco DevNet Associate

SQL Intermediate (Sololearn)

NDG Linux Essentials

Optimizing test automation with

centralized test data (Tricentis)

Software Testing and Automation

Specialization

SPECIALIZED TRAINING IN JAVA

Functional Programming in Java 18: API Stream Java 18: Clean Code Java 18: Concurrency Java for QA

ADRIANO DÍAZ BENÍTEZ BACKEND DEVELOPER

Backend developer specialized in Java and Spring Boot. I have knowledge in Python and C# (.Net) and experience in functional test automation projects with Selenium (Java and Python). Over 30 repositories on my GitHub where you can see my personal projects: www.github.com/PublioElio. Passionate about technology and continuous learning, I feel comfortable working in international environments (C1 English Certification by Cambridge).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Functional Tester QA - Sogeti

March 2024 - june 2024

Automated testing programming with Selenium in Java/Cucumber and Python/Behave. Functional, accessibility, performance, integration, and end-toend testing. QA management with Jira and Xray. Project management with Scrum (Professional Scrum Master Certificate).

Programming Instructor - Aspasia - SEPE - Euroformac

November 2019 - March 2024

Courses Taught:

- Analysis and Programming in Java
- Mobile Application Development on **Android** with Java
- Java Application Development: Web Components and Database Applications (Hibernate - JSP and JPA) - Spring Boot.
- Software Project Management and Development Methodology with Scrum
- Internet Security with **Linux**
- Web Development for E-commerce

Backend developer - IntegraQuatro

September 2016 - December 2017

Digitalization Project for SMEs: Development of Cross-Platform Applications in Java. Cloud Deployment with AWS. My main focus was on backend programming, including database creation and the use of Spring Boot. Testing with JUnit.

Front-end Programming: Form design, landing page layout with CSS. Functional web page testing. UX/UI development.

EDUCATION

2024 Software Testing and Automation Specialization

Online specialization course that includes: Introduction to Software Testing, Black-box and White-box Testing, Introduction to Automated Analysis, and Web and Mobile Testing with Selenium. Technologies used: JUnit, Mockito, Cucumber, Selenium, Behave and Appium.

2023 Development of Cross-Platform Applications

- Management and design of databases
- Configuration of development environments (NetBeans, Eclipse, IntelliJ, Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio, Android Studio, PyCharm)
- Development of cross-platform applications with database access
- Languages used: Java, Python, C#, and JavaScript; Spring Boot.
- Development of graphical user interfaces. UX/UI design.

2022 School 42 Málaga (Fundación telefónica)

Bootcamp. Fundamentals of software development with **C** language and version control with Git. Installation and configuration of computer systems with Linux. Bash scripting.

- Master's in Corporate Communication Management
- 2009 Bachelor's in Journalism